hello my name is green and welcome back
to another episode of hermitcraft it
turns out that i'm not the only one that
doesn't want this mansion
no one has come to buy this at all so um
i think immediately the first thing we
need to do is lower this
price for sale 50 diamonds there we go
half price 50 off please someone buy
this mansion it's not that ugly
right let's head over to sahara very
very quickly i've got a few jobs that i
want to do in today's episode including
a bit of spring cleaning it's it's not
spring it's obviously winter still it's
only january but um i think it's time we
did a bit of cleaning so i said this
last episode but actually i've been
saying this for a few episodes i want to
finish
this but i need more white concrete so i
remade
this
but the issue is i didn't know what to
do so
um i'm just gonna do it anyway
and hope for the best that's honestly
the best i can do as far as i'm aware
it's not too difficult but you know
knowing me this is going to end very
very badly so as far as i'm aware the
only bit of trickery is that this
detector rail right here
needs to be placed facing north or south
so i think it's as simple as that
basically you put the minecart on
you put the tnt
somewhere
oh it's got to be right under it
oops
okay
[Laughter]
so dead coral here
tnt
here
and then you put the minecart
well that didn't work
yeah i'm doing something wrong all right
about a little look at a tutorial
and
it's it's yeah it's a little bit more
trickery than i thought you can't just
set it up exactly how it was
okay
i think that's it i need to activate it
once maybe so
i think that's it i think that's it
activated it's not blowing up oh my
goodness oh my goodness is this it did i
do it
oh no no no no no no no
wait it did work
it did work
it's alive
i thought
it looks like it's going to blow up
there though
oh it is it is
why why
hey
what on earth
what did i do wrong
i know exactly
exactly what i did wrong there we go
that's better
now let's let's do this thing again
and this time everything's going to be
okay
it's gonna be okay
oh this is mildly annoying
mildly annoying
i definitely did something wrong here
i feel like it was something very stupid
like one block of white concrete out of
place
and it stopped the tnt or i was one
block over ah okay right let's let's
remake this thing
the first time it seemed like it was
working and i must have gotten away with
it but then
yeah now i now i know what mumbo is
saying
wise words of mumbo he said something
along the lines of hey green make sure
you uh make sure you do this properly or
it's gonna blow up
okay
it's done again i really don't want to
have to make this for a third time i
think i know what was wrong i didn't
have these furnaces full maybe and maybe
some of these timings were off and
that's what did it it's as simple as
that this controls um this down here
which i mean it's kind of hard to
explain but it's actually fairly simple
um after making this a few times i
actually understand how it works so this
controls the exact time to release the
tnt and then it holds it here for just a
second so that it can explode in the
middle of the air now my issue i think
was that my timings were all wrong so
when i turned this off there was still a
tnt left here
explosion so i just need to activate
this
that has primed the tnt
and then
uh that looks like it's working that
seems to be about right so let's just
give this a quick test so if i start
placing some concrete powder yeah as
well seems to be working okay let's
start printing there's a stack
i think this i think this is working
and now
the big question will it turn off
hey
oh
the mustache has done it i did it i did
it i did it i did a redstone okay right
i
i did do a redstone
however i've got to admit this isn't my
design or anything but i did make it
work and i do understand it i could
probably build this again i understand
things so what now now
we can get going on printing out the
rest of
my white concrete to be honest most of
this will be fine uh if i'm going to be
building half of it underground so now
what i'm going to do is spend quite a
lot of time getting the white concrete
together to build the rest of this we're
going to make two more of these as i
promised a long time ago but now we're
actually going to do it so another time
lapse here we come so i'm going to whiz
through these time-lapse segments a
little bit quicker than usual just
because the build on this isn't actually
that interesting it's literally the four
corner thing and it's just to decorate
and well finish my build but i i didn't
want to waste too much time with it so
there we are it's done easy
there we go it is officially finished
now the the this is really embarrassing
um i didn't actually need to fix the tnt
machine i actually have quite a lot of
concrete powder left over
so
that was a little bit unnecessary but at
the same time i did blow this up so it's
probably a good idea that i sorted it
out so i pressed tab as well
look at iskall's face what it what is
going on what
what
i even i don't even want to know so
there's one more thing that i want to do
in this episode and it's to do with
these the numerous shulker boxes that i
own now you might remember a long time
ago i actually put in my bucket list to
do a hermitcraft is an item sorter
and even on my second layer of my base i
actually started putting things into
chests well actually i didn't i made the
chest but i never actually did anything
with them hey look some tnt okay
yeah i didn't do much with these so what
we're going to do we're going to go on a
little mission
we're going to go and collect
all of the shulker boxes that i've left
strewn across this map i'm going to try
and find all of them and we're gonna
we're gonna sort this mess out this
chest monster has gotten out of hand and
it's time to put a stop to it so we can
kick things off by putting all of these
shulker boxes in and now we have to try
and remember where we've left everything
because that's another problem i have no
idea where half the stuff is i know that
i've my most recent project was over
here and of course there's a load of
shulker boxes
this is going to be
ridiculous
now here's the issue with this whole
situation i've got so many shulker boxes
that i don't know what to do with
and i really should have made a item
system the problem is we're so far into
season six i mean look at that already
i've only done one trip we've got loads
more to go and get
we're so far into season six that it
almost seems pointless making
an item filter or sorter at all the
minigame district and hippie land
probably has a bunch of shulker boxes
for us to collect
you know in season 7 i am 100
making an item sorter
very very quickly as soon as i have the
materials that is one of the things
that's happening i am not letting this
happen again oh yeah there's loads in
this house as well i think i've got a
problem i genuinely think i've got a
little bit of an issue
look at this so many shulker boxes
and you know what there's probably more
down here as well
i completely forgot about this little
room in here
so i'm inconsistent with where i leave
them there was one shulker box in here
oh there's even there's more upstairs
oh my goodness
i don't have the space i genuinely don't
have the space for all of these
okay i could put some in my ender chest
over here
and then i could collect more
this is gonna be several trips i think
in order to get all my stuff
think this is mine the issue is i'm not
the only one on this server that leaves
shulker boxes absolutely everywhere so
you've got to try and identify which
ones are yours i cleared this out and
yet no one wants uh no one wants this
this is still for sale there's probably
way more locations that i've just
forgotten about
this one is probably where
most of them are as well because i know
i've left a lot here
spring cleaning
yep run out of space
okay right we've got to take all these
back now another trip this is going to
take a little while actually
okay
round two the chest monster grows and on
this episode of hoarders
green has a serious issue with shulker
boxes he can't seem to throw anything
away
and it's starting to pile up on him
oh my goodness
[Laughter]
there's just so much rubbish everywhere
okay right we need to go and get even
more stuff i actually need some
fireworks
see this is part of the problem i
actually need things and there's
probably some fireworks somewhere in
here
but who knows where i mean just look at
the rubbish in here there's probably
nothing useful in any of these
whoa
that might come in handy
okay a couple more collections and uh
i think i might have found most of them
by now
and that's not even including the stuff
that's in normal chess that i've just
left lying around
okay i think i've got all of the chests
from this area i've checked all the
projects that i've done
oh man this is looking awesome i'm
waiting i'm waiting very patiently
for this to open talk about shulker box
monsters
this is something that i've been waiting
for this is a
boom box by tango and i don't want to
spoil anything but that is a game that
isn't quite open yet but i'm really
hoping that i can play it soon because
well i i'm still you have to remember
i'm still new to hermitcraft i might
have been playing for two years but i
haven't been part of any other season so
this is a game that he's made previously
but i've actually never got to play okay
building it up even further
this is ludicrous
this is way bigger than i ever thought
this was gonna be
yeah that's
that's uh that's an issue that is a
solid shulker box monster
or am
or am i the monster
this has been a mess this has been a two
year long mess in the making and i'm
slightly proud of it in a weird way
i'm slightly proud of it now i can't
find any more but i'm pretty sure
there's still loads of shulker boxes
around probably even in places like
sahara i've left some shelter boxes just
lying around wait what about the dragon
bro base
probably left loads in there
oh please don't be trapped
please don't be trapped i'm not in the
mood for more trappage yep i knew it i
knew it there's always more there's
going to be loads of these everywhere we
may even have to look further back in
time maybe i left some shulker boxes
back here at the g team base i mean this
was a really long time ago but i have a
feeling i did empty the shulker boxes
here
but uh i'm not entirely sure
you know what i can't even remember how
we get into here i think oh yeah there
might be somewhere at the back oh yeah
here we go
oh wow this is this is a trip down
memory lane nope yep there's some
shulker boxes okay to be fair this is
mostly empty but there's still shulker
boxes
wow this really is a trip down memory
lane it's been a long time since we were
here okay i did i did gut the place
there is there is nothing here
hold the phone
yes please
oh my goodness how many firework rockets
did i make it's always useful to go and
uh explore this sort of thing okay i'm
i'm convinced now i've done a proper
look around you've only seen part of it
but i've i've looked at all my projects
now
and i'm pretty sure i've gotten most of
the stuff i'm not really entirely sure
what to say about this other than
oopsie
we could be looking at several hours
work
well more than several hours work tens
of hours of work
to get this in an item sorter or even
just manually sift through this stuff
and put it upstairs it could take days
or
i could just leave this in the season
six download and um you know this is a
bit of a monument and this is a promise
to myself
be better
do do not do this next season
this is embarrassing
everyone's embarrassed okay now we have
this shulker box monster ready it's time
to actually store it away and you know
because of this because of this pile of
shulker boxes i think well there's got
to be consequences i'm not gonna be
making the items sorted like i said i
would at the beginning of the season and
for some reason you guys are holding to
me something like i said like two years
ago but what we're gonna do
we're gonna make a chest monster
and it's not gonna be pretty it's not
gonna be pretty
so
let's do it
so i'm actually speaking you know after
i've made this so i know what you what
you're about to see and it's um just
brace yourself like hold on to your
chair um you know put your hands hands
firmly grasping something because this
is this is weird this is
come from a very strange place i had a
bit of help from don rao and together
this has come from our minds this is a
chest monster like you've never seen it
and i must admit this is quite the
punishment it even needed arms like it i
this started out as just a weird idea
and then it just it just kept going it
just kept going and going and going i
was like yeah i have to make a chess
monster i have to punish myself so i
made this weird
thing
it's stuck in the ground and then it
went even further and i was like yeah
okay so it needs legs and the legs of
course have to pop out through so this
chest monster
is a bit of art it's um it's
representing
yeah my struggle
it
i don't i i
don't think i can look at this
without laughing
this is this is like art i don't know
how else to describe it i think this has
come from my soul okay this has come
from a place this is like the
representation this is a physical
manifestation of my
problem with sorting items it's even got
all of these chests either side and it
isn't such
he's in such agony this is the real
representation of the chest monster
and my issues and the worst thing is
this genuine
this genuinely ruins my base a little
bit i'm not gonna i'm not gonna lie
it has ruined my base because
you could you could see him through at
any point because it's all made out of
glass
it just oh it looks so dumb
it looks so dumb especially as i haven't
actually put anything inside any of the
other layers oh okay i've got a garden
there i got a completely empty layer
and then ah he looked oh my goodness
from this angle he looks so sad
and then he looks uh i don't know what
expression that is it's it's just um
struggle
that's struggle
okay so now what we need to do is take
the actual
chest monster here which is actually
going to take me a little while because
i uh
yeah it's a lot of bot it's a lot of
blocks there so let's get started let's
take all this
and start moving it all upstairs fly
into the mouth so i've made a decent
amount of space in here and then off we
go we just gotta we just gotta start
placing them now these items are gonna
be pretty much unusable
from now on so if i if i actually need
anything out of these it's gonna be even
more of a pain to get my hands on stuff
this build has genuinely brought a bit
of a tear to my eye i can't i can't
quite take it seriously i also can't
believe i built this thing i don't know
what's come over me this is so weird
this is just such a weird thing
to build i don't i don't know why i've
done this you know this actually kind of
doubles as a prank
because
here's the thing on hermitcraft loads of
the hermits ask for items all the time
but i don't usually include it in my
videos
but you know we all go like how has
anyone got emerald blocks has anyone got
some quartz i can use like you know
that's that sort of trading stuff
happens all the time if especially if
there's not a shop for it and it's like
yeah yeah sure you know just just head
over to my base and grab some so this is
gonna end up being a hilarious prank
because this is now technically
my new item storage my new item sorter
so if anyone asks me
can i borrow this this or this i'll say
yeah sure no problem just go and check
my item storage
and lo and behold they'll have to come
and see this thing and then they'll have
to look through all of these boxes and
realize they can't even open the ones on
the bottom
oh man i think probably one of my
favorite things about this
are the little feet
this guy looks like he needs a name he
needs a name what's his name is it just
the chest monster i think it is the
chest monster but he he genuinely looks
like he's stuck
this is what you should all be thinking
of
when you see a chest monster on the
floor and i think i think scar
actually could do with one of these you
know what this actually looks pretty
cool with all of these shulker boxes
here in the mouth like this
it actually looks awesome
i just actually think there might be
more shulker boxes than he can eat
i genuinely i genuinely can't wait for
someone to come and have a look for
something you know what the problem is
though actually it's probably going to
be me isn't it it's it's you know i've
just thought about this
for a second i've let this this thought
process in my mind the person who's
going to need these shulker boxes the
most
is me
and i'm gonna i mean i'm used to looking
through shulker boxes but not like this
not like this this is insane i should
have at least i should have at least
like gone through them and taken the
ones that have actual value
most of them have rubbish it like look
i'm never gonna use a loom 63 books a
couple of weird red banners and some
thorns like you know there's just
there's some utter trash in most of
these boxes
but yet some of them maybe i can hit
gold on one of them
look this one freaks i'm gonna need you
know what i'm gonna need those this i
gotta keep those somewhere
ridiculous and i think that one that one
had the redstone blocks it you know some
of these have like this one rubbish
that's a rubbish one that this one here
mega value what am i playing at this is
a terrible idea but i'm still gonna do
it
rubbish rubbish rubbish
rubbish
uh useful
okay i've kept some some of the useful
ones at least
i'm really gonna regret this i i mean
i'm kind of already regretting this just
because of the impact that the chest
monster has on my base it was such a
beautiful elegant base and then
[Music]
oh yeah it loads in there that's awesome
this looks cool i mean it's weird but
it's cool
okay let's take a step back take a look
at this and appreciate
look at those chat look at those shulker
boxes in there it proper fills that up
oh my goodness what have i created
a monster i have created a monster but
he's he's kind of cute kind of
terrifying kind of weird and makes me
feel uncomfortable but at the same time
this is
a physical
representation of my struggle
for keeping shulker boxes organized
there must have been 100 shulker boxes
in there easily
and i think with that that is the end of
what way to end an episode that is the
end of the episode everybody and oh my
goodness i don't know how you feel about
this i kind of feel a bit
i kind of feel a bit weird about all
this
but uh i'd like to see your comments um
should he have a different name should
we name him i think chess monster is
fine personally but i'm afraid that is
all we have time for today thank you
very much for watching everyone and
thank you so much and i mean this if
you're watching uh to the end of the
video which not many people do so if
you're here well well done um thank you
so much for being patient with me either
you know life hits you hard sometimes
and it's not always easy to make videos
i will be trying my best to make more
and more and more but you know sometimes
sometimes life comes at you fast and uh
well i'm looking forward to seeing where
whatever this thing goes
alright thank you very much for watching
and good bye